ANDERS GRØN

2300 Copenhagen S, Denmark (+45) 61 28 32 10 \diamond anders.barslund.green@gmail.com

PERSONAL

My goal is to work for an organization which provides me the opportunity to improve my skills and knowledge within public leadership, social innovation, research, and data science. Check out my personal website for more information.

EDUCATION

Aarhus University, Denmark

MSc in Political Science

St.Gallen University, Switzerland
Summer school, Econometrics of Big Data

Essex University, England

Sept. 2017 - Feb. 2020

GPA: 3.8/4.0

Summer 2019

Grade: none

Summer 2018

Summer school, Machine Learning for Social Scientists Grade: 93/100

London School of Economics, China

Summer 2018

Summer school, Big Data: Data Analytics for Business and Beyond

Grade: A

WORK EXPERIENCE

Crown Prince Frederik Center for Public Leadership, Aarhus

Sept. 2020 - present

PhD Fellow

Responsible for planning and executing a project focusing on collaborative public leadership. See below.

Rockwool Foundation, Copenhagen

Feb. 2018 - July 2020

Data Analyst

Responsible for planning and executing data analytic work in relation to scoping, developing, and evaluating real-life RCT-based interventions ranging from basic descriptive statistics and graphing to advanced machine learning. Improved project facilitation and leadership competencies.

Aarhus BSS, Aarhus

June 2016 - June 2019

Teaching Assistant

Taught for five semesters in four different subjects. Improved pedagogical and structuring competencies.

PHD PROJECT

Project description: Teamwork makes the Dream work?

Description will follow.

Courses, seminars, conferences, etc.

List will follow.

PROJECTS

Machine Learning

Description will follow.

Edx.org

Description will follow.

Shiny

Description will follow.

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

Modeling and Analysis Software & Tools STATA, R, Python MS Office, Latex

\mathbf{EXTRA}

Podcaster and writer at my personal website.

PUBLICATIONS			
Will be updated.			
OTHER			

Will be updated.